truebloodnet.com 2018-10-17

# Privacy Policy : True Blood News- ALL the True Blood Season 7 Spoilers Videos Interviews

Browse >

[Home](https://truebloodnet.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

**Updated May 24, 2018**

What is personal data?

We collect information about you in a range of forms, including personal data. As used in this Policy, “personal data” is as defined in the General Data Protection Regulation, this includes any information which, either alone or in combination with other information we process about you, identifies you as an individual, including, for example, your name, postal address, email address and telephone number.

We respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at Truebloodnet.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Truebloodnet.com.

Truebloodnet.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. We collect information from online visitors who ask to be on our newsletter mailing list and/or receive periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can choose to be removed from our mailing list at any time.

All online visitor data collected by Truebloodnet.com is protected against unauthorized access. We will not sell, trade, or give your personal information to other companies or organizations.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. Truebloodnet.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child’s online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child’s information is treated.

Check out the [FTC’s site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html) for more tips on protecting children’s privacy online.

### Log Files

We may use log files to track visits to Truebloodnet.com. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personal identifiable information.

### Cookies

This site does not use cookies. However, Advertising services such Google Adsense use cookies on Truebloodnet.com. We have no access to and can not control these cookies.

**What is a Cookie?**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are.

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.

**There are two different types of cookies:**

1) Session Cookies: These are temporary and are erased when you close your browser at the end of your surfing session. The next time you visit that particular site it will not recognise you and will treat you as a completely new visitor as there is nothing in your browser to let the site know that you have visited before.

2) Persistent Cookies: These remain on your hard drive until you erase them or they expire. How long a cookie remains on your browser depends on how long the visited website has programmed the cookie to last.

### Beacons

This site does not use beacons. However, Advertising services such Google Adsense use cookies on Truebloodnet.com. We have no access to and can not control these beacon logs.

**What is a Beacon?**

A beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

For example a company owning a network of sites may use web beacons to count and recognise users travelling around its network. Being able to recognise you enables the site owner to personalise your visit and make it more user friendly.

### Outgoing Links

Truebloodnet.com may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware that when they leave Truebloodnet.com to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Truebloodnet.com.

### Advertisers and Affiliate Companies

Truebloodnet.com uses outside ad companies to display ads, such as Google Adsense. These ads may contain cookies that are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. To the best of our knowledge, we follow all ad and affiliate company privacy policies. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

### Links to Advertisers and Affiliate Companies Privacy Policies

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:

Truebloodnet.com

Email: privacy@truebloodnet.com
